《异形4：复活》
(奥瑞戈军医研究太空船)
(船舰组员: 军人42人 科学家7人)
My mommy always said there were no monsters.
我妈说世上没有怪物
No real ones.
真正的怪物
But there are.
可是真的有
We've seen no additional defects.
我们没见到多余的瑕疵
- She's perfect.   - Mm-hmm.
- 她很好  - 嗯
Careful.
当心
Two centimeters.
2公分长
Okay.
好的
Yeah.
Ready with that amnio.
准备剪破羊膜
- Oh.   - And...
- 噢  - 对了...
there it is.
出来了
No.
不
Be careful.
小心点
Jesus.
天啊!
Clamp.
夹住伤口
What about her? Can we keep her alive?
她怎样?可以留她活口吗?
How's the host?
寄主状况如何?
Doing well.
"寄主"很好
Sew her back up.
替她缝合伤口
Excellent work, everybody.
做得非常好
And how is our Number 8 today?
8号今天如何?
Appears to be in good health.
健康情况良好
- Hmm? How good?   - Excellent,
- 多好?  - 非常好
as in completely off our projected charts.
胜于其他复制人
Look at the scar tissue.
你看她的疤痕
- See the recession?   - This is from three days ago?
- 有凹陷吗?  - 3天前的伤口?
- Exactly.   - Oh, this is good.
- 没错  - 很好
This is very good.
非常好
You're gonna make us all very proud.
你将让大家引以为荣
No.
我没事
Don't. I'm all right.
不!我没事
Now try this.
试试这个
- Hand.   - Close.
- 手  - 很接近
Glove.
是手套
Number 8?
8号
Fruit.
水果
- Good. Cherries.   - It's unprecedented.
- 很好,樱桃  - 史无前例的
Totally. She's operating...
绝对是,她具有...
at a completely adult capacity.
成人的行为能力
- What about her memories?   - There are gaps.
- 她的记忆呢?  - 有些部份无法串连
- And some degree ofsynaptic dissonance.   - You know this.
- 某种程度的不协调  - 你知道的
- She's freaked.   - Come on.
- 她很怪异  - 加油
It has connective difficulties,
会有沟通障碍
caused by a biochemical imbalance, causing emotional autism.
生物化学产生的情绪自闭
- Certain reactions   - All right, wait a second!
- 某些反应...  - 且慢!
It has memories. Why does it have memories?
她有记忆,她怎么会有记忆?
Well, I'm guessing, but... inherited memories,
我猜是...遗传
passed down generationally at a genetic level...
如异形般代代遗传...
by the aliens, like its strength.
就像她的力气
Plus a, uh, highly evolved form of instinct.
再加上高度进化的本能
An unexpected benefit from the genetic crossing.
配种基因的意外收获
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho. I see.
噢!噢!噢!噢!噢!我明白了!
Stupid me. Ofcourse.
我真蠢
An unexpected benefit ofthe genetic process.
配种基因的意外收获
Oh! And I didn't even think ofthat!
我居然没想到!
Let's try this one.
现在试试这个吧
Ripley?
蕾普莉
Ripley.
Ripley, what is it?
蕾普莉,怎么了?
Ripley? Ripley?
蕾普莉?蕾普莉?
You're not thinking termination?
你不是想除掉她吧?
Oh, boy, am I thinking termination.
我当然想!
General, we do not perceive this to be a problem.
将军,不用担心她
Ellen Ripley died trying to wipe this species out.
海伦·蕾普莉死于致力消灭异形
For all intents and purposes, she succeeded.
她差不多取得了成功
I'm not anxious to see her taking up her old hobbies.
我不想她重操旧业
- That won't happen.   - We won't tell her.
- 不会的  - 我们不会告诉她
Oh, I see. And that's supposed to comfort me?
我就能安心了?
Identification, please.
身份核对
Please try again.
请再试一次
Thank you, General Perez.
谢谢,裴瑞将军
Bottom line is, she looks at me funny one time,
若有异状
I'm putting her down.
立刻消灭她
Okay, as far as I'm concerned, Number 8...
对我而言,8号...
is a meat... by-product.
只是一个副产品
Her Majesty here is the real payoff.
异形王后才值回票价
- When does she start producing?   - Days.
- 何时能产卵?  - 或者要几天
Less maybe.
或许更快
- We need the cargo.   - I told you, it's on its way.
- 急需那批货  - 我说过快到了
Fork.
叉子
- Fuck.   - It's-It's "fork."
- 操  - 是叉子
How did you-
你们怎么...
How did... we get you?
怎么...制造你?
Yes.
是的
Hard work. We used blood samples...
不简单,我们取得...
from Fiori Sixteen on ice,
舰上冰冻血样本
where you died.
你命丧的地方
We've remade you. We cloned you.
再造你,复制你
Fiori Sixteen.
佛奥十六号
Does that ring a bell?
不是太美妙吗?
Are you remembering something?
想起任何事吗?
- Does it grow?   - Yeah.
- 它长大了?  - 是的
Very rapidly.
它长得很快
It's a queen.
是王后
How did you know that?
你怎么知道?
She'll breed. You'll die.
她会产卵,你们会死
Everyone in the company will die.
机构所有的人都会死
In the-In the-In the company?
机构?
Weyland-Yutani. Ripley 8's former employers.
伟伦优达尼公司,蕾普莉8号生前的雇主
Terran growth conglomerate. They had...
负责人类发展的联合企业...
defense contracts under the military.
与军方签了合约
Oh, they went under decades ago, Gediman. Way before your time.
几十年前就没落了,那是好久以前的事了
Bought out by Wal-Mart.
被威名百货合并收购了
Fortunes ofwar.
战争的收获
I thinkyou will find that, uh,
你将会发现...
things have changed a great deal since your time.
时代不同了
I doubt that.
我怀疑
We're not flying blind here, you know.
这不是盲目行动
It's United Systems Military, not some greedy corporation.
这是军队,不是贪婪的机构
Well, it won't make any difference.
没什么分别
You're still gonna die.
你们还是会死
How do you feel about that?
你觉得如何?
I wish you could understand what we're trying to do here.
希望你明白我们的目的
The potential for this species goes way beyond urban pacification.
想想看由它来镇压暴动
New alloys, new vaccines.
或研发出特殊金属与疫苗
Nothing like this we've ever seen on any world before.
前所未见
You should be very proud.
你该感到光荣
I am.
我是的
And the animal itself-
那种生物
wondrous.
不可思议
The potential, unbelievable, once we've tamed them.
训练后,它的潜力将无可限量
Roll over. Play dead.
翻身、装死
Heel? Mm-hmm.
坐下
You can't teach it tricks.
你不能教它杂耍
Why not? We're teaching you.
为何不能?我们教你了
(贝蒂商用货机 组员6名 未注册)
Hey, son, I'll give you my authorization code.
小子,我告诉你密码
It's E-A-T-M-E.
是EATME(吃我)
I'm sorry, sir. Could you repeat that?
请重复
Little prick.
坏家伙
You know,
知道吗?
no matter how many times you see it,
每次见到这个
the sight ofa woman all strapped up in a chair like thatjust-
女人像这样被绑在椅子上...
What?
怎么样?
Just bring us in on a 3-0 descent, would ya?
请准备降落
- And ride the parallel.   - Darlin', it is done.
- 保持平衡  - 已经就绪
Good girl.
乖女孩
You, uh, want anything there, trigger?
想要什么吗?
Hmm. Yeah. How 'bout a cup ofcoffee?
来杯咖啡怎样?
Anything else, while your mouth's warm, I mean?
还要喝点什么?
Little milk.
加点牛奶
Hey, don't cut thrust till about 600 meters,
到六百公尺再停
and we'll give 'em a little scare.
吓吓他们
Vriess. Call.
瑞斯,柯儿
Lock down. We're gonna dock.
可恶,我们会死掉的
(消磁)
- Hey, Call?   - Yep?
- 柯儿?  - 什么事?
What has two thumbs, one eye,
什么东西有两只拇指,一只眼睛
a pink tongue...
红舌头...
and screws like a god?
还会扮鬼脸的?
What?
什么?
Two thumbs, one eye, a pink tongue...
两只拇指、一只眼睛、红舌头...
and screws like a god?
还会扮鬼脸的?
What?
什么?
Time to enjoy some of the general's hospitality, Christie.
是时候享受将军的热情款待
Great. Army food.
太好了,军队食物
Yeah. It'll do till we get the family wagon up to spec, I reckon.
待武装登舰就知道了
Yeah. That is ifthe natives are friendly.
若他们够友善的话
How's that?
情况如何?
Good.
很好
We expecting any, uh, trouble?
会有麻烦吗?
Nah. From Perez, I doubt it. But you never know. We've been there before.
裴瑞将军?不会,但说不定,以前已尝试事
What is wrong with you?
你怎么了?
Just a little target practice.
练习射靶
Vriess isn't complaining.
瑞斯没投诉
Goddamn it!
可恶!
Johner, you son ofa bitch!
强纳,混蛋!
Come on, man. You didn't feel a thing.
行了!你根本没感觉
You are an inbred motherfucker, you know that?
你这狗娘养的
I'll take the knife back now.
刀给我
Call, forget it.
算了吧
He's been sucking down too much home brew.
他已经喝多了
The knife.
刀给我
Son ofa bitch!
臭婆娘!
Don't push me, little Call. You hang with us for a while,
别惹我,相处一段时间后
you'll find out I am not the man with whom to fuck!
你会知道我是不好惹!
It's about time we start associating with a better class of people.
不要和这种低级人一般见识
I am Father.
我是"父亲"
Welcome to the U.S.M. Auriga.
欢迎登上奥瑞戈舰
Step forward for contraband and weapons search.
上前通过违禁品检查
Please report any infectious diseases...
若有传染病...
to the medical officers.
请向医务官报告
Levels 7 through 12 are off-limits to civilians.
7到12层,平民勿入
Thank you foryour cooperation.
谢谢合作
Go.
走
- Get your hands up, please, sir.   - What?
- 举起手  - 什么?
Could you get your hands up, please?
举起手
There are no weapons allowed on board, sir.
不准携械登舰
My own recipe.
独家调配烈酒
Way more dangerous.
这更危险
Nice welcome, Perez. What the hell is this?
这么热情欢迎,为什么?
What, are you afraid the six of us are gonna hijack your damn ship or what?
担心我们六个人劫舰?
Just a minor concern that one ofyour asshole crew members...
只是要肯定你们组员之中...
is gonna get drunk and put a bullet through the hull.
不会因喝醉乱开枪
We happen to be in space, Elgyn.
我们在太空中
- No shit.   - How you been?
- 没错  - 你好吗?
Wanna check the chair?
要检查椅子吗?
Elgyn, these were very, very hard to come by.
艾金,这是千载难逢的机会
So was our cargo.
这批货也是
- You're, uh, not about to plead poverty on me, are you, General?   - No.
- 你不是向我喊穷吧?  - 不是
Just saying very few people deal in cash nowadays.
但近来很少用现金交易
Just the ones don't like to keep business records.
因为有人不想留下纪录
- Yourself, for example.   - Drink, Elgyn?
- 你也一样  - 有喝酒吗?
Constantly.
常喝
Now, I'm gonna take a wild guess here, General,
让我猜猜看
but I'm thinking whatever you got going on here,
你们进行的研究
it, uh, ain't exactly approved by Congress.
未经国会认可
Who's the...
那个...
new fillyyou got on board, Elgyn?
新来的组员是谁?
Call. Little girl playing pirates.
柯儿,海盗学徙
She makes an impression.
她美丽动人
She is severely fuckable, ain't she?
令人蠢蠢"欲"动
Mighty handy with a monkey wrench too, I might add.
真是灵活妙手
I think Vriess has got a bit ofa light in his eye for her.
瑞斯看着她的眼神,好像很着迷
Fine little ass like that'd make a man walk. You know what I mean?
那种尤物令跛子也会走路,明白没有?
Mind you, uh, I think she'sjust a tad curious...
提醒你,她对我们的交易...
about, uh, this little transaction ofours.
很好奇
I mean, I can't say as I blame her.
不能怪她
It's awfully cloak-and-dagger stuff.
太神秘了
It's a military operation.
军事运作
- Really?   - Mm-hmm.
- 是吗?  - 嗯
Correct me if I'm wrong, but, uh,
我若说错请纠正
I was under the impression that, uh,
据我所知
most army medical labs don't have to operate outside of regulated space.
一般军医实验不会在监查范围外运作的
- What do you want, Elgyn? What can I do foryou?   - Me?
- 你到底想怎么样?  - 我?
- Yeah.   - Oh, two days bed and board.
- 是的  - 两天的食宿
You know, Vriess might wanna snag a part here or there, whatever.
瑞斯可能会偷点医药用品
I mean, uh, if it's not imposing.
若你不介意的话
I don't see any problem.
就当在家一样
Couple ofconditions though. Ah.
但是有几个条件
Conditions?
条件?
Not you...
你自己...
nor any ofyour...
与那批...
formidable crew members...
勇猛组员...
will go anywhere near...
都不可接近...
restricted areas.
禁区
Rule number two:
第二点:
No trouble.
别惹麻烦
- Good behavior.   - Good behavior.
- 循规蹈矩  - 循规蹈矩
- No fights.   - No fights.
- 不准打架  - 不准打架
Mi casa es su casa.
其他没了
Please direct cargo to med lab center, area "G."
请将货柜送入实验中心
Follow the lit path.
跟随指示
Do not deviate.
请勿越界
Cargo status: stable.
货柜状态: 稳定
Life-forms intact.
生命迹象稳定
Stasis uninterrupted.
休眠中
Med lab center is off-limits to civilians.
实验中心,平民勿入
Thank you.
谢谢
- Oh.   - Hey. Chill.
- 噢  - 嘿,丘尔
- Oh, please.   - You know I can't lay offthe tall ones.
- 拜托  - 我不喜欢高大的女人
Howyou doin'? How about a little one-on-one?
你好吗?一对一?
What do you say?
意下如何?
You got some moves on you, girl.
球技不错
Oh, man.
噢
Mm-hmm.
嗯
Well, now, ifyou don't wanna play basketball, I know some other indoor sports.
若不想打篮球,我们还能玩点别的室内运动
Come on, now. Give me the ball.
球给我
Okay, I got a new game.
我有新游戏
Tag!
中招!
Ripley? Ripley.
蕾普莉,蕾普莉
You've had enough fun.
玩够了
What the hell are you?
你是谁?
Something ofa predator, isn't she?
她很厉害
Yes, she continues to make us all very proud.
对,她不断令我们引以为荣
We're coming up on just one minute and 30 seconds left...
订购此收藏品的时间...
to order this one-of-a-kind collector's item.
只剩下1分钟30秒
Jesus Christ,Johner, what do you put in this shit, battery acid?
天!这是什么?电池液?
Just for color.
加了颜色会好看点
So, we're a fast learner.
它学得很快
Now here's a fine item. This is a really good show, man.
这节目很棒
It's from the Gut Cutter's Celebration Collection,
来自科特公司...
makers of premier knives and edge ware.
刀具和刃具的主要生产者
The knife features a stainless steel blade,
其生产的刀具很锋利
perfect for any use in hunting or in the home.
打猎、切菜,样样行
The pro handle is made from authentic antique plywood...
刀柄是用高级木材制作的...
and stained in brilliant colors for an uncanny charm.
不掉色,又好看
Hey, man, that shit is not easy to come by!
嘿!这些酒得来不易!
Why don't you take a walk outside?
给我滚出去
...to a cutting edge that will rip through anything-
...几乎能切开任何东西
Great!
岂有此理!
- I'm so sorry.   - Now I smell like this shit!
- 很抱歉  - 弄得我混身臭味!
If bitches can't handle this shit,
要是不会喝
bitches should stay away from this shit!
就别逞强!
Go to bed. Fucking bitch.
上床,贱人
Identification, please.
身份核对
Please try again.
请再试一次
Thank you, General Perez.
裴瑞将军,谢谢
Well?
怎样?
You gonna kill me, orwhat?
你要杀我吗?
There's no point, is there?
没理由杀你
They've taken it out ofyou.
异形生下来了
Where is it? Is it on the ship?
哪里?在船上吗?
You mean my baby.
你指我的孩子?
I don't get it. Ifthey took it out,
我不明白,他们取出异形
why are they keeping you alive?
为何不杀你?
Well, they're curious. I'm the latest thing.
他们很好奇,我是新实验
Look.
看...
I can make it all stop.
我能阻止一切
The pain, this nightmare. That's all I can offeryou.
解除你的痛苦与噩梦
What makes you think...
何以见得...
I would let you do that?
我会让你这么做?
Who are you?
你是谁?
Ripley, Ellen, Lieutenant First Class,
海伦·蕾普莉,一级中尉
number 36706.
编号36706
Ellen Ripley died 200 years ago.
蕾普莉两百年前就死了
You're not her.
你不是她
I'm not her.
我不是她
Who am I?
我是谁?
You're a thing, a construct. They grew you in a fucking lab.
你是实验室的制成品,她们再造了你
And now they brought it out ofyou.
现在还用你生下它
Not all the way out.
不是原来的我
I can feel it... behind my eyes.
我能感觉到...它就在我眼前
I can hear it moving.
能听到它移动
You gotta help me stop this thing before it gets loose.
趁还来得及你得帮我阻止
It's too late.
太迟了
You can't stop it.
你阻止不了
It's inevitable.
避免不了
Not as long as I'm around.
有我在,休想
You'll never get out of here alive.
你无法活着离开
I don't care.
我不在乎
Really?
真的吗?
I can make it stop.
我能阻止它
Go on. Get out of here.
快走!快离开!
They're looking foryou.
他们在找你
I think you're gonna find that this was very ill-advised.
你这样做简直愚不可及
- Where are her friends?   - They're in the mess hall, sir.
- 她的朋友呢?  - 在餐厅
Well, you find them, now. Quietly.
立刻找来,别作声
What the hell is going on here?
什么回事?
Smells like a double-cross, boss.
他们背叛我们
Where's the other one? With the chair?
坐轮椅的呢?
Don't ever touch me.
别碰我
Ever.
永远别碰我
You wanna tell us what this is?
究竟什么回事?
- You wanna tell me who you're workin' for.   - What?
- 你们替谁工作?  - 什么?
- Wren, they got nothing to do with this.   - To do with what?
- 此事与他们无关  - 什么事?
Do you know what the penalties for terrorist activity are?
知道恐怖行动的刑罚吗?
No goddamn terrorists on my crew. Call, there something you wanna tell me?
我们当中没有恐怖份子,什么回事?
Look. I don't care whether you knew or not. You brought a terrorist on board a military vessel.
不论你知情与否,你带恐怖分子上军舰
And as far as I am concerned, you all die with her!
我认为你们都该死
Do you understand?
明白吗?
Yeah.
是的
I understand.
我明白
Christie.
克里斯蒂
Down!
趴下!
Freeze!
不准动!
Stop! Drop your weapons!
住手!丢下武器!
And you! Drop that piece ofshit, or I blow his head off!
你!丢下武器!否则杀死他!
- Can't do that, man.   - Drop it now!
- 做不到  - 立即抛下!
- Can't do that. They're attached to me.   - I'm not fucking with you!
- 做不到,他们隶属于我  - 我可不是说笑!
You're all under arrest for a code eight, which is concealed weapons,
你们全部因私藏枪械被捕
and a code 12, which is murder!
还有第十二号规例,谋杀罪!
- Release Dr. Wren!   - Kiss my ass.
- 放开瑞温博士!  - 去你的
Put down yourweapons and assume the fucking-
放下你们的武器,保证...
Everybody okay?
大家还好吗?
Real easy, soldier boy.
别紧张,阿兵哥
- Security.   - Get up!
- 保安!  - 起来
There is a serious problem in the mess hall.
安全室餐厅发生严重暴动
You lie to me now, little girl,
你敢骗我...
I will cut your throat and leave you here to die, you understand me?
我会割破你的喉咙,叫你死在这里,听到没?
- This is security, Section 2. We do not read you.   - Hello? Goddamn it! Hello?
- 这是二号保安区  - 喂?妈的
We do not copy you. Please repeat.
听不到,请再说一次
- Hello?   - Please repeat.
- 喂  - 请再说一次
Gediman!
杰狄!
He's conducting illegal experiments. He is breeding some sort of-
他进行非法实验,他繁殖...
- Ice the goddamn mole!   - Listen to me! He is breeding an alien species.
- 杀了她!  - 听我说!他在培育异形
More than dangerous. Ifthose things get loose,
它们极之危险,若让异形逃脱...
it's gonna make the Lacerta plague look like a fucking square dance!
到时等于人类末日,最后大家同归于尽
Shut up!
闭嘴!
Listen.
听着
Your attention, please.
请注意
Security breach, med lab, Level 15.
紧急情况,在第15层实验室
Go. Let's get back to the Betty. Doctor and soldier boy here can see us to the door.
快回贝蒂号,出口没人看守
- What about Vriess?   - Fuck Vriess.
- 瑞斯怎么办?  - 有空管他
Your attention, please.
请注意
Unauthorized opening ofcage three.
擅自闯入3号门
Unauthorized opening ofcages five,
擅自闯入5号门
seven, eight, 10-
7号、8号、10号门
- Move it! Now!   - Evacuation.
- 快走!  - 撤离!
- Go! Go now!   - Evacuation.
- 走!  - 撤离!
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
- Evacuation.   - Move it! Go! Get on board!
- 撤离!  - 快上去!
Your attention, please.
请注意
Nonhuman presence detected,
侦测到非人类生物
Levels 21, 23,
在第21层、23层
27, 14,
27层、14层
Level 38, Level 39.
38层、39层
Evacuation.
撤离!
Proceed to lifeboats.
登上救生船
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
Thank you for your cooperation.
谢谢合作
I'll give you holes, you slimy bastard!
杀死你!恶心的混蛋!
Move it! Let's go!
走!快!
- Final lifeboat ready for launch.   - Get aboard!
- 救生船准备起飞  - 上船!
Go!
走!
Complete evacuation now.
立即撤离
Grenade.
手榴弹
Alert. Alert.
警报!警报!
Evacuation incomplete.
未完全撤离
Civilian presence detected in area "H." Warning.
H区发现尚有平民,警告
Main vessel declared uninhabitable.
船舰不适合人类驻留
Elgyn, come on. Let's move, man.
艾金,来,我们走
Yeah.
是
Elgyn? Elgyn, where are you?
艾金?艾金,你在哪里?
Elgyn, where are you?
艾金,你在哪里?
Elgyn?
艾金
Elgyn!
- God. Elgyn?   - Elgyn?
- 天哪,艾金?  - 艾金?
Elgyn!
艾金
Easy, Hillard! Christie, give me a hand here!
小小,哈立德!克里斯蒂,帮我一把!
- Get him up!   - Give me a hand here!
- 扶起他!  - 帮我一把!
- Come on! Let's get him up!   - Move out of the way!
- 快!扶起他!  - 滚开!
- No!   - Ah, shit.
- 不!  - 噢,惨了!
- What the fuck did this?   - What's in this place?
- 是什么弄的?  - 什么鬼东西?
- Call, get down!   - What the fuck is that?
- 趴下  - 那是什么?
Don't shoot! It's in front ofthe hull!
别开枪,会射到船身
What is that?
那是什么?
- Come on, man. Time to go. Time to go!   - Get back!
- 快离开!  - 回来!
Damn!
去死!
Call, time to go! Come on, Call!
柯儿!走了!快点!柯儿!
Get the goddamn door open!
快打开门!
We can't open it! We can't open the door!
打不开!打不开门!
- We gotta go back!   - I'm not going back! You go back!
- 得回头去!  - 我不去!你去!
What the fuck?
他妈的什么回事?
Was it everything you hoped for?
如你所愿?
Leave him alone!
别碰他
What do we do now, man?
现在怎么办?
- Same thing we're doin'. Get the hell outta here!   - What if there's more?
- 老样子,离开这鬼地方!  - 假如还有异形呢?
I say we stay here, man. Let the army guys deal.
留在这里,让军人处理
Where the fuck are the army guys?
军人在哪里?
They're dead!
都死了
Well, then we don't need this asshole anymore.
我们不需要他了!
- Step back!   - No, you step back!
- 退后!  - 不,你退后!
- Stop it!   - You got no authority here!
- 别吵!  - 轮不到你指挥!
Doctor, that thing that killed my partner,
博士,杀我同伴那东西...
- that's your pet science project?   - Yes.
- 就是你的实验品?  - 是的
- Let me do him right now, man!   - I should let him do you right now!
- 我杀了他!  - 应该让他杀了你!
How many more are there?
还有多少异形?
- How many more are there?   - Twelve.
- 究竟还有多少只?  - 12只
- Twelve?   - Twelve.
- 十二只?  - 十二只
Twelve.
十二只
There'll be more.
还会有更多
So,
那么...
who do I have to fuck to get off this boat?
我要跟谁干才能离开这里?
I can get you off. Maybe not the boat, but...
我来,不一定能离开,但是...
- Let's get out of here.   - No, wait a second here.
- 快走  - 不 且慢!
She was the host for these monsters.
她是这些异形的宿主
Wren cloned her because she had one inside her.
她体内有异形,所以瑞温复制她
She's not human.
她不是人类
She was part of his experiment, and she will turn on us in a second.
她也是实验品,随时翻脸不认人
I don't give a shit what she is.
我不管她是什么
She's too much ofa risk. We have to leave her.
太冒险了,不能带她走
- She comes.   - We can't trust her!
- 带她走  - 我们不能相信她!
I don't trust anyone.
我谁也不信
If we're gonna survive this mess, we all stick together.
想活命就要团结一致
Agreed?
同意吗?
Hillard, we gotta go. It's not over. We gotta get to the Betty.
哈立德,我们走,事情还没完结,我们要回贝蒂号去
Make a nice souvenir.
不错的纪念品
I can't believe you did that.
没想到你会那么做
- Did what?   - Killed one of'em.
- 做什么?  - 杀死异形
- It's like killing your own kind.   - It was in my way.
- 杀你的同类  - 它阻我去路
Oh, man!
天啊!
Who were you expecting, Santa Claus?
你以为是谁?圣诞老人?
Thought you were toast for certain, man.
我以为你死了
Shit. Where's Elgyn?
艾金在哪里?
Oh, shit.
妈的
Hey, man, what if we get to the Betty and they're all over it?
若异形都在贝蒂号上呢?
All the activity's been in the aft sector by the barracks. Why would they move?
所有活动都在舰尾的兵营发生,它们为何要转移阵地?
They won't.
不会
Ifthey send anyone out,
假如异形出来了
it'll be, uh, here,
会来这里
where the meat is.
有人肉的地方
Yeah. Well, I say ifwe wanna make any decent time, I say we ditch the cripple.
为节省时间,该甩了那跛子
- No offense, man.   - None taken.
- 恕我直言  - 没关系
Nobody is left behind. Not even you,Johner.
不可以丢下任何人,包括你
- What's the quickest way out of here?   - After the cooling tower,
- 哪条路是捷径?  - 冷却塔后
there's a freight elevator.
有运货电梯
It runs from the top ofthe ship down to Engineering Level 1 deck.
由舰顶直通舰底
- Take us straight to the dock.   - Sounds reasonable. Let's do it.
- 直达码头  - 很好,就这么办
We're moving.
船在移动
- What?   -  The ship is moving.
- 什么?  - 船在移动
I can feel it.
我感觉得到
The ship has stealth run. There's no wayyou can tell.
船是超静动力,你不可能感到移动
She's right.
她说得对
The ship's been go since the attack.
异形攻击后船就动了
- That's a standard emergency procedure.   - That's right.
- 这是标准紧急程序  - 对
Any serious problem, and the ship autopilots back to home base.
遇上任何危机,船就自动回航
And you were planning on letting us know this?
你打算何时才告诉我们?
Nobody asked.
没人问我
What's home base?
基地在哪里?
Earth.
地球
Oh, great.
惨了!
- Bastard.   - Earth?
- 混蛋!  - 地球?
I'd rather stay here with the things, man.
我宁可被它吃了
How long until we get to Earth?
多久到达地球?
Three hours almost.
大概3小时
We gotta blow the ship.
必须炸了船
Call, you're not blowing this ship.
柯儿,不能炸掉船
Not while we're on it, okay?
除非离船之后
We get out ofthis shit, you do as you please, all right?
离开后随便你炸
Earth, man. What a shit-hole.
地球是个烂地方
It's clear.
没有异样
Hey, Ripley.
蕾普莉
I heard you, like, ran into these things before.
听说...你跟异形交手过
- That's right.   - Wow, man.
- 没错  - 厉害
So, like, what did you do?
那当时你怎样做?
I died.
我死了
Not that way!
走错路了!
Ripley.
蕾普莉!
Ripley, come on.
蕾普莉,快走!
Ripley, we got no time for sightseeing here.
蕾普莉,没时间观光
Ripley, don't.
蕾普莉,别这样
Kill... me.
杀了...我
Kill me.
杀了我
Don't do it, Ripley.
不要,蕾普莉
Don't do what?
不要什么?
What's the big deal, man?
这样做何苦呢?
Fuckin' waste ofammo.
浪费弹药
Let's go.
走!
Must be a chick thing.
女人才会这样
Am I dreaming, or is this not the shit we brought with us?
是我在做梦吗?这是我们带来的货?
Yeah, it's the same shit.
对,就是他们
Stinks in here, man. Let's keep moving.
臭死了!走吧!
Get away from me! Get away from me!
离我远一点!离我远一点!
- Drop the rod, man.   - Get away from me!
- 抛下棍子  - 离我远一点!
- Do it!   - Get away from me.
- 抛下!  - 离我远一点!
Get away from me.
离我远一点!
Who are you people?
你们是谁?
- What's happening here?   - Calm down.
- 发生什么事?  - 冷静点
What's happening here is we're getting the fuck off this ghost ship, okay?
我们必须离开这个鬼船
Ship? What ship?
什么船?
Where am I?
我在哪里?
I was in cryo, right? On my way to Xarem, right?
我在冰温舱,去撒伦星,对吗?
Work crew for the nickel refinery, right?
我是铸币工人
I wake up. I know I don't understand.
我醒来,我不明白...
Oh, God. Uh, I s-I saw-I saw horrible things.
天啊,我看到可怕的事情
Look, you're coming with us. It's too dangerous for you here.
跟我们走,这里太危险了
Leave him.
留下他
Fuckyou. We're not leaving him here.
去你的!不能留下他
He's got one inside of him.
他体内有异形
I can smell it.
我闻得出来
Inside me?
在我体内?
- Inside me? What's inside me?   - Hey, man.
- 我体内有什么?  - 天啊
I don't want one ofthose things birthing anywhere near my ass.
我不想有异形出生
It's a bad risk.
太冒险了
- What's inside me?   - Look, we can't just leave him here.
- 我体内有什么?  - 不能留下他
- I thought you came here to stop 'em from spreadin'.   - What's inside me?
- 不希望它们繁殖吧?  - 我体内有什么?
- There's gotta be a process. Can't you stop it?   - Got no time for that.
- 一定有办法!能阻止吗?  - 没时间
- I can't do it here. The lab is out oforder.   - What's inside me?
- 无法在这里做  - 我体内有什么?
I could do him. Back ofthe head.
我可以向他后脑开一枪
Painless. It might be the best way.
不会痛,这样最好
- What's inside me?   - No, there's got to be another way.
- 我体内有什么?  - 不要这样,一定有其他办法
- What ifwe freeze him?   - What's in-fuckin'-side me?
- 冷藏他?  - 我体内到底有什么?
A parasite!
寄生虫!
Foreign element.
有个外来生物
There's a monster in your chest.
你胸部有个怪物
These guys hijacked your ship,
他们夺走你的船
and they sold your cryo tube...
把冰温舱卖给...
to this... human,
这个人
and he put an alien inside ofyou.
他将异形植入你体内
It's a really nasty one.
很恶心的那种
And in a few hours, it's gonna burst its way through your rib cage...
几小时后...它会穿破你胸膛...
and you're gonna die.
你会死去
Any questions?
还有问题吗?
Who are you?
你是谁?
I'm the monster's mother.
我是怪物的妈妈
Look, he comes with us, we freeze him on the Betty,
听着,他跟我们走,我们将他冷藏在船上...
- then the doctor can remove it later.   - Fine with me.
- 稍后再让医生把异形弄掉  - 这下好了
Since when were you in goddamn charge?
你几时变成指挥官?
- Since you were born without balls!   - Ease off, people.
- 从你变成胆小鬼开始  - 不要吵了
All right. You come with us. You might even live.
好了,你也来,可能有机会活着
Get twitchy on me, and you'll be shot.
要是你敢妄动,就必死无疑
Let's move out.
大家走吧
It's a mess down there! Is this the only way?
一塌糊涂!只有这条路?
Vriess, we gotta lose the chair.
瑞斯,你不能再坐轮椅了
I know.
我知道
Kawlang maneuver, all right?
我背你过去,好吗?
- Yeah,just like old times.   - Yeah.
- 对,就和以前一样  - 对
Must be the cooling tanks.
一定是冷却槽
Somebody must have opened the valves.
有人开了水阀
The nasties couldn't have done this, could they?
不会是异形吧?
We're at the bottom ofthe ship.
我们在船底
We have to go through the kitchen, maybe 90 feet,
要经过厨房,约90尺
to the freight elevator on the other side.
到另一端的货运电梯
- I don't like it.   - What's to like?
- 我不喜欢  - 谁管你?
This sucks!
糟透了!
- Wren, are you sure about the distance?   - Yes.
- 你确定距离?  - 对
- You ready to get wet, partner?   - Yeah.
- 准备好浸湿了吗?同伴?  - 嗯
Hey, uh, do your weapons fire underwater?
武器浸过水没问题吧?
- Yeah, they're disposables. They can take it.   - Disposables?
- 这是即弃型武器,没问题  - 即弃型?
Hey, I heard about those. Yeah.
我听过这种武器
- How many rounds?   - Twenty.
- 有几发子弹?  - 20发
Split points give you a good hole, even at the smaller caliber.
口径虽小,火力可不小
Oh. Hey, that's cool.
真厉害
Yeah. They're big with hitters 'cause you, uh, throw 'em away after thejob.
杀手最喜欢用的,杀光了就可以丢掉
Nobody likes to throw away a weapon they're attached to. You know what I mean?
连在身上的武器,我可抛不掉
Yeah.
懂
Guess I don't have to tell everyone to take a deep breath.
不说也知道,要深深吸口气吧
Hey, Christie, do me a favor.
克里斯蒂,帮帮忙
When we hit the surface on the other side,
当我们游到对岸时...
no backstroke, okay?
别用仰泳,知道吗?
Jesus Christ!
天!
They set a goddamn trap.
它们设了陷阱
It's a goddamn ambush!
有埋伏!
Distephano!
上去!
It won't break. Give me yourweapon.
打不开,枪给我
You really are way too trusting.
你太信任别人了
No!
不!
You killed her! You bastard!
你杀了她!混蛋!
I'll get you!
去死!
Father, lock the door.
"父亲",锁上门
Christie! Climb! Climb!
克里斯蒂!快爬!
- I'm doin' it, man!   - Come on!
- 我在爬!  - 加油!
Come on!
加把劲!
- It's jammed!   - Move it!
- 卡住了!  - 快爬!
It's jammed
卡住了!
Get off my foot, bitch!
放开我的脚,贱人!
Get off me!
放开我!
Johner!
强纳!
Get off me! Get off me!
放开我!放开我!
Aaah!Johner!
啊!强纳!
Die, motherfucker!
死吧!混蛋!
Do it, man!
杀死它!
Hey!
嘿!
Real nice party, ain't it?
很刺激吧?
Christie! Christie!
克里斯蒂!克里斯蒂!
Christie! No!
克里斯蒂!不!
Christie!
克里斯蒂!
What are you doing? Don't do it!
你干什么?别这么做!
Don't! We can make it!
不!我们会成功的!
No!
不!
Damn!
妈的!
This way.
这边
Come on!
快点!
Baby, am I glad to see you.
孩子,真高兴见到你
I was sure that asshole got you. Are you hurt?
那混蛋打中你一枪,受伤了吗?
I'm fine.
我没事
- You got body armor on?   - Yeah. Come on.
- 你穿了防弹衣?  - 对,走!
You took it in the chest. I saw it.
我看到你胸部中弹
You're a robot?
你是机器人?
Son ofa bitch! Our little Call isjust full ofsurprises.
贱货!真令人惊讶!
I should have known. No human being is that humane.
我早该料到没这么完美的人类
I thought synthetics were supposed to be all logical and shit.
和机械人讲逻辑
You're just a big old psycho, girl.
你却像疯子
- You're a robot?   - You're a second gen, aren't you?
- 你是机器人?  - 第二代机器人?
You're an Auton.
奥谭型机器人
Robots designed by robots, right? Hah!
机器人造的机器人
Oh, yeah. That's right. I remember.
对了,我想起来了!
Now, they were supposed to revitalize the synthetic industry.
本来预期复兴合成人工业
Instead, they buried it.
后来却全毁了
They didn't like being told what to do.
他们不听命行事
Government ordered a recall.
被政府收回
Now, I heard-I had-I had heard...
听说...
that only a few-just a few-had gotten out intact.
只有很少数流入市面
Man, I never, never thought that I would see one!
我没料到能亲眼见到!
Great. She's a toaster oven.
太好了,她是烤面包机
Can we leave now?
可以走了吗?
How long before we land?
多久到达地球?
- Just under two hours.   - Hey, Vriess.
- 不到两小时  - 瑞斯
You got a socket wrench? Maybe shejust needs an oil change.
有螺帽吗?或者她只需换油?
- I'm sorry. Access denied.   - I can't believe I almost fucked it.
- 对不起,不准进入  - 我差点与她做了
Yeah, like you never fucked a robot!
你又不是没毁过机器人!
You know, ifWren gets in the computer, he could really screw us.
你知道,如果瑞温接上电脑,我们就完了
- We gotta find a terminal.   - No, there's no console on this level.
- 必须找到终端机  - 这里没操控台
- We'd have to go back.   - Well, we can't go back.
- 必须回头  - 不能回头
- And I don't know any ofWren's access codes.   - Help me.
- 我不知温的密码  - 帮我
Call.
柯儿?
No. I can't.
我不行
Right. You're the new model droid.
你是新机型
- You can access the mainframe by remote.   - No, I can't.
- 能遥控操作主机  - 不行
I burned my modem. We all did.
我烧了数据机
Call, you can still patch in manually. You know that.
柯儿,你还是能转回人手操作,你懂得的
There's ports in the chapel, up there.
上面有个电脑接口
Call.
柯儿
- You're programmed for that?   - Don't make me do this.
- 你的程式是这么设计的  - 别逼我
Don't make me make you.
别让我逼你
I don't want to go in there.
我不想进入
It's like my insides are liquid. It's not real.
我感觉好虚幻,不是真的
Get over it.
克服它
You can blow the ship before it reaches Earth...
到达地球之前将船炸毁...
and kill them all.
杀光它们
Just give us time to get out first.
给我们时间逃出
- Damn it.   - Anything?
- 可恶  - 有资料吗?
Hold on.
等一下
Breach in Sector 7, Sector 3.
7区、3区受损
Sector 9 unstable.
9区不稳定
Engines operating at 41 %.
引擎运转指数41%
Eighty-six minutes until Earth dock.
86分钟后抵达地球
We burned too much energy.
船的能源受损
I can't make critical mass. I can't blow it.
无法将船炸掉
Then crash it.
那就撞毁它
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我没事
Really.
真的
I feel good.
我很好
Ground level recalibrated.
重新调整底层
New destination: 7-6-0-4-0-3.
新目的地7-6-0-4-0-3
Uninhabited quadrant.
朝无人之地飞行
Braking systems off-lined. Acceleration increase.
自动减速系统关闭,减速增快
Time until impact now 43 minutes, 8 seconds.
距离撞毁还有43分8秒
Try to clear us a path to the Betty...
清空往贝蒂号的路...
and start her up.
启动贝蒂号
Okay.
好的
Please wait.
请稍候
Emergency override in console 45V, Level 1 .
45操控台输入新指令
It's Wren. He's almost at the Betty.
瑞温在搞鬼,他就快到达贝蒂号了
Father, locate the power drain. Report.
父亲,回复电力,请回答
Father? Father!
父亲!父亲!
Father's dead, asshole.
父亲死了,混蛋!
Intruder on Level 1 .
第一层有入侵者
All aliens, please proceed to Level 1 .
异形请到第一层集合
You got a mean streak.
你真够狠毒
- Damn it.   - Let me see.
- 可恶!  - 让我看看
- Don't touch me.   - Come on.
- 别碰我  - 别这样
You must think this is pretty funny.
你一定觉得很有趣
I'm finding a lot of things funny lately,
最近发现很多有趣事
but I don't think they are.
但我觉得并非真的有趣
Why do you go on living?
你为何要活下去?
How can you stand being what you are?
你能接受这个事实吗?
Not much choice.
我没有选择余地
At least there's a part ofyou that's human.
至少你有一部份是人
- I'm just   - Look at me.
- 我只是...  - 看看我
I'm disgusting.
真恶心
Why did you come here?
你为何来此?
To kill you, remember?
来杀你,记得吗?
Before the recall,
被收回前
I accessed the mainframe.
我进入主机
Every dirty little covert op the government ever dreamed of is in there.
政府所有最机密下流的秘密行动都在里面
And this-you, the aliens,
有你、异形
even the crew from the Betty-I knew ifthey succeeded, it would be the end ofthem.
和贝蒂号的组员,计划成功,人类势必灭亡
Why do you care what happens to them?
与你何干?
Because I'm programmed to.
我被程式控制
You're programmed to be an asshole?
你被设定成混蛋?
You're the new asshole model they're putting out?
你是新上市的混蛋机型?
Come on.
帮帮忙
I couldn't watch 'em do it.
这种事我看不下去
I couldn't let 'em annihilate themselves.
不能让人类自我灭绝
Do you understand that?
你明白吗?
I did once.
本来明白
I tried to save... people.
我试图救人
It didn't work out.
但是没有用
There was this girl.
有个小女孩
She had bad dreams.
她会发恶梦
I tried to help her.
我想救她
She died.
她死了
Now I can't even remember her name.
我记不起她的名字了
I guess we're almost there.
快到了吧?
Right.
对
Do you dream?
你会发梦吗?
I-Well, we have neuroprocessors that-Yes.
我们有神经系统
When I sleep, I dream about them-it.
我发梦就会梦到异形
Every night. All around me, in me.
每个晚上,到处都是,也在我体内
I used to be afraid to dream, but I'm not anymore.
本来我怕发梦,现在不怕了
Why?
为什么?
Because no matter how bad the dreams get,
因为每当我发了恶梦
when I wake up, it's always worse.
醒来见到的比梦境更可怕
- It's not so far now!   - God, I'm so tired.
- 离贝蒂号不远了!  - 天啊,我累死了
Sleep when you die, man.
死后可睡个够
Oh, no. This is bad, right?
糟!情况不妙!
- I think we're near the nest.   - Well, then we'll go another way.
- 接近异形巢穴了  - 我们走别条路
- We don't have time.   - We got nearly 90 minutes.
- 没时间了  - 还有90分钟
- Not anymore.   - What are you saying?
- 不是了  - 什么意思?
- What did you do, robot?   - Let's go. Come on.
- 你做了什么?  - 走了
Hey! You want to die here with your little brothers and sisters, that's cool!
你想跟其他的人死在这里,随便你!
But I plan to live past today!
但我还想活!
If this little hunk of plastic is pulling any shit,
这机器人敢耍花样...
I'm gonna kill her!
我就杀死她!
Kill you! Does that compute?
杀死你!理解没有?
Or do I have to drawyou a schematic?
要我画图表给你吗?
Hey!
嘿!
You want another souvenir?
还要纪念品?
- How far are the docks?   - A h-hundred yards.
- 离码头有多远?  - 100码
Ripley.
蕾普莉
Come on.
快走
Ripley, we have to go.
蕾普莉,我们要走了
I hear them.
我听到它们
I hear them. They're so close.
我听到它们,它们离我们很近
- Ripley.   - It's the queen.
- 蕾普莉  - 是王后
She's in pain.
它很痛苦
Ripley!
蕾普莉!
Wait!
等等!
Oh, my God.
我的天
We gotta be moving.
我们要走了
The best thing you can do is pray for a quick death.
只能祈祷她死得快些
Come on. Come on.
走吧!
It's not right.
这样不对
I've been saying that all day.
我见惯不怪
It's up to you now, Call.
柯儿 全靠你了
I need you to patch into the ship again and open the hatch.
再接上电脑,打开舱门
Johner, we should put Purvis in the freezer now.
把他放入冰温舱中
All right, little buddy.
来吧
Nap time.
小睡片刻
Nobody moves, or I put a cap...
别动,否则轰了...
right where this little droid's brain is.
她脑袋
Distephano, take the weapons.
达斯,拿掉他们的枪
Begging your pardon, sir, but fuckyou!
对不起,长官,但是去你的!
Oh, fine. Then I kill her, and you kill me,
我杀死她,你杀死我
and we all die, and nobody goes home!
大家都要死,别想回家!
Now drop the weapon.
丢下武器
Then this little synthetic bitch...
让机器人...
is gonna plug into the Auriga,
接上奥瑞戈号
and she is gonna take us right back to home base,
带我们回基地去
according to the standard emergency procedures.
就按标准程序去做
- No, she's not.   - Are you crazy?
- 不,休想  - 你疯了?
You still want to bring those things back to Earth?
还想将异形带回地球?
- Haven't you been paying any attention today?   - Ah, the intellectual speaks.
- 你到现在还不明白?  - 智者说话了
- Stay there!   - Listen, ifyou don't...
- 别动  - 听着,如果你不...
Don't you ever shut up?
你闭嘴行不?
Why does nobody listen to me?
为啥没人听我的话?
I told you. At first, everything was normal.
我说了,开始很正常...
The queen laid her eggs. But then she started to change.
王后产卵,突然变了
She added a second cycle cell.
还有另一个巢
So,
所以...
this time there is no host.
现在不需宿主了
There are no eggs.
不产卵了
There is only herwomb...
只需要她的子宫...
and the creature inside.
孕育怪物
That is Ripley's gift to her:
蕾普莉给她的礼物:
A human reproductive system.
人类再生系统
She is giving birth foryou, Ripley,
因为你的缘故...蕾普莉
and now she is perfect!
它已臻完美!
You are...
你是...
a beautiful,
美丽的
beautiful butterfly.
美丽的蝴蝶
No.
不!
No. No.
不!不!
Ah, look. Look.
看看
Beautiful, beautiful little baby.
美丽的小宝贝
Look. It thinks you're its mother.
它当你是母亲
Come on.
来啊
来啊!
Yeah.
对!
Come on.
来!
Civilian vessel on line.
民用太空船连线
Emergency departure authorized.
批准紧急撤退
All right. She's hot. I'll open the Auriga's air locks, pull the holding clamps on your mark.
太热了,要打开气密门,缩回夹钳
Right. I-I just need to find, uh, the, uh-
好,我得找到...
th-the vertical thrust lock.
垂直推进器
- Are you sure you guys can fly this thing?   - Yes!
- 你们会驾驶吗?  - 会!
- Launch status is go.   - No!
- 准备发射  - 不!
Ripley.
蕾普莉
- Hey.   - I thought you were dead.
- 嘿  - 我以为你死了
Yeah, I get that a lot. Why are we still here?
我听惯了这句,怎么还没走?
Uh, I'm just, uh, finding the, uh, manual override.
我在设法用人手操作
- For Christ's sake.   - Hey, Ripley.
- 天啊!  - 嘿,蕾普莉
Good memory. Excuse me.
我记性好,抱歉
- Ripley's back, man.   - Is that it?
- 蕾普莉回来了  - 是那个吗?
Nope.
不是
You can't fly one of these things too, can you?
你会驾驶这艘船吧?
Are you kidding? This piece ofshit is even older than I am.
开玩笑,它比我还老
Goddamn it. We've still got breach. The hatch.
糟糕,舱门没关
- I closed it.   - Fixed the goddamn hatch a hundred times, man!
- 我关了  - 舱门每次都出问题!
I'll get it. I'll get it.
我去处理
Approaching Earth's atmosphere.
接近地球大气层
Window ofdeparture now 46 seconds.
安全驶离时间还剩46秒
Call, we have to go.
柯儿,我们要走了
Call.
柯儿
We've gotta get out of here.
我们必须离开
Window ofdeparture now 20 seconds.
安全驶离时间还剩20秒
Grab on to something, Call. We're outta here.
抓稳,我们要走了
Come on, baby.
加油
This thing is gonna fall apart.
船身快裂了
Pressure's unstable!
压力不稳!
Go help Call turn on the auxiliary pump!
叫柯儿开启备用气泵!
Distephano?
达斯?
Come on! Step on it!
快啊!加速!
Hey, I'm not the mechanic here, Ironsides!
嘿,我又不是机械师,勇士!
I mostlyjust hurt people!
我只会杀人!
Shit. Call!
混蛋!柯儿!
Call, get back up here!
柯儿,快回来!
Call! Call!
柯儿!柯儿!
Ripley! Hey, Ripley!
蕾普莉!嘿!蕾普莉!
Johner, where are you, you son ofa bitch?
强纳,你在哪?你这婊子养的?
- Get on it, bastard!   - What am I supposed to do?
- 快过来!混蛋!  - 我该怎么办?
Grab the sticks.
抓紧控制杆
Put her down.
放下她!
Ripley!
蕾普莉!
Oh, no!
不!
I'm sorry.
对不起!
No!
不!
U.S.M. Auriga will impact in five seconds.
奥瑞戈号5秒后撞毁
Four. Three.
四秒、三秒
Two. One.
二秒、一秒
Thank you.
谢谢
- What's burnin'?   - Us!
- 什么东西起火了?  - 是我们!
Shit! You're right!
妈的!你说对了!
So this is Earth, huh?
这是地球?
This is Earth.
这就是地球
This is my first time here.
我第一次来这里
I suppose the military will be sniffing around here pretty soon.
军队很快就会找到我们
Bet you're not too anxious to see them.
你好像很失望
Not really.
的确是
You know, a person could get pretty lost around here ifthey wanted to.
在这种地方很容易迷路
What do you think?
你觉得如何?
What should we do?
我们该怎办?
I don't know.
不知道
I'm a stranger here myself.
我也是第一次来这里